Guide to the Langdon Kingsley Storm Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Langdon Kingsley Storm papers
1917-1946
1917-1936
MS 1876
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
The papers include memorabilia, photographs, and publications related to Langdon Kingsley Storm's years at Yale (1917-1921) and his last year at the Collegiate School (1917).
Storm, Langdon Kingsley
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Enid S. Dwyer, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Langdon Kingsley Storm was born March 9, 1899, in New York City. He attended the Cheshire (Connecticut) School and the Berkeley and Collegiate schools in New York City. He graduated from Yale University in 1921. His professional life centered on work as an advertising executive with Charles M. Storm Company, Inc. He married Helen Payne Bacon in 1925, and their daughter, Enid, was born in 1926.
Scope and Contents
The papers include memorabilia, photographs, and publications related to Langdon Kingsley Storm's years at Yale (1917-1921) and his last year at the Collegiate School (1917).
Arrangement
The papers are arranged by type of material.
Storm, Langdon Kingsley; Collegiate School (New York, N.Y.); Yale University -- Students
- Inventory, 1917-1946
  - Memorabilia
    - "Mind My Place" [place holder], undated (Box 1)
    - Yale Class of 1921 banner, undated (Box 1)
    - Yale fraternity paddle [probably associated with Zeta Psi fraternity], 1919 (Box 1)
  - Photographs
    - Collegiate School, Class of 1917 (Box 2)
    - Yale, Class of 1885, undated (Box 2)
    - Yale, Class of 1921 (Box 2)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 2)
  - Publications
    - The Dutchman [Collegiate School yearbook], 1917 (Box 3)
    - A History of the Class of 1921, Yale College (Box 3)
    - "Hoops of Steel" [privately printed for William Burnett Benton with accompanying correspondence from Benton to Storm], 1936 April 1, 3 (Box 3)
    - The Quarter-Century Chronicle, Class of 1921, Yale College, 1946 (Box 3)
    - The Yale Record, Vol. 48, 1919-1920 (Box 4)